{
    "id": "f03eddabb41748e8823e26195f2e8a3e",
    "title": "Commonly Confused Words And Phrases",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "30c05e4d51684059af56de4e80601ed0",
            "title": "Commonly Confused Words And Phrases",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ............................... him that we had not paid the utility bill yet.",
                    "description": "We remind someone to do something they might forget. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "reminded",
                        "remembered",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'm afraid I won't ............................... his face.",
                    "description": "Remember and remind have different meanings. To remind is to make someone remember. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "remind",
                        "remember",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We use only the bedroom and the kitchen. ............................... of the house is empty.",
                    "description": "The rest means what is left. The article 'the' is always used in this expression. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Rest",
                        "The rest",
                        "The remains"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... of the meal were lying all over the floor.",
                    "description": "We can use the word remains to talk about what is left after something has been used up. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "The rest",
                        "Rest",
                        "Remains"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You and Peter can take four chocolates each. The rest ............................... mine.",
                    "description": "When the rest refers to a plural noun, the verb is plural. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Show me ............................... again.",
                    "description": "We normally use the article the before same. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "same",
                        "the same",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have got ............................... .",
                    "description": "We use the same as before a noun or pronoun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "the same problem as me",
                        "the same problem like me",
                        "my same problem"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is the same man ............................... asked me for directions yesterday.",
                    "description": "Before a clause we can use the same ... that / the same ... who",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "'Turn left, 'I ................................'",
                    "description": "We use tell when there is an object. If there is no object, we use say.",
                    "answers": [
                        "said",
                        "told",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ............................... me that she would come.",
                    "description": "We use tell when there is an object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "said",
                        "told",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We will ............................... that problem tomorrow.",
                    "description": "When see means think or consider, a preposition is necessary before the object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "see about",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... this color suits you.",
                    "description": "See can be followed by if or whether. This expression has the same meaning as find out. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "See if",
                        "Look if",
                        "Watch if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}